runnable.com 2018-11-27

# Our Privacy Policy — Runnable

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, or use a Runnable environment. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, phone number or employer. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * **To personalize your experience** —your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs. 
  * **To improve our website** —we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 
  * **To improve customer service**
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. 
  * **To send periodic emails** —the email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

**Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your information?

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to the privacy policy terms on this page. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on April 18th, 2016. 

## Contacting Runnable

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#c0b0b2a9b6a1a3b980b2b5aeaea1a2aca5eea3afad) or at the address below: 

**Runnable**  
1481 Folsom Street  
San Francisco, CA, 94103  
USA
